A spy is never out of the game.
The November Man is a crime, action, thriller film directed by Roger Donaldson.
An ex-CIA operative is brought back in on a very personal mission and finds himself pitted against his former
pupil in a deadly game involving high level CIA officials and the Russian president-elect.
Peter H. Devereaux, played by Pierce Brosnan.
David Mason, played by Luke Bracey.
Alice Fournier, played by Olga Kurylenko.
Hanley, played by Bill Smitrovich.
Alexa, played by Amila Terzimehić.
Arkady Federov, played by Lazar Ristovski.
The November Man is a 2014 spy action thriller film based on the novel There Are No Spies by Bill
Granger, which is the seventh installment in The November Man novel series, published in 1987.
A British-American production, it stars Pierce Brosnan, Luke Bracey and Olga Kurylenko, with Bill Smitrovich
and Will Patton also appearing, with the screenplay written by Michael Finch and Karl Gajdusek.
The film is directed by Roger Donaldson, who previously
worked with Brosnan on Dante's Peak.
The film was released on August 27, 2014 in the United States.
The film depicts an attempt to use photographic evidence of Russian war crimes in the Second Chechen
War against a new Russian President-elect who was directly involved in the crimes.
The film explores themes of central intelligence agency (cia),
based on novel or book, retired, agent, montenegro.
The tone is intense.